<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects on Forty</title>
    <link>/projects/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Projects on Forty</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 20 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/projects/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Covid 19 Mortality</title>
      <link>/projects/project2/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/project2/</guid>
      <description>Analysis of mortality rates based on several input variables On this page, we are going to look in more detail at the deadliness of Covid-19. We know that the virus has spread across the world over the last few months, sending terror into the minds of billions worldwide. However, is it as deadly as we think it is? Is there evidence to show that people must be extremely worried about this virus.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Does the Yield Curve Predict a Recession?</title>
      <link>/projects/project4/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/project4/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Every so often, we hear warnings from commentators on the “inverted yield curve” and its predictive power with respect to recessions. An explainer what a inverted yield curve is can be found here. If you’d rather listen to something, here is a great podcast from NPR on yield curve indicators.
In addition, many articles and commentators think that, e.g., Yield curve inversion is viewed as a harbinger of recession.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Donald Trump&#39;s Approval Rating</title>
      <link>/projects/project3/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/project3/</guid>
      <description>A personal forecast of the upcoming US election The race is on. Four years after Trump’s historic election victory, the time has come again this November - the 52 American states will elect a new president. As of today, Biden is far ahead in the polls.
This may be due to the policies of real estate magnate and incumbent president Trump, but most of all, his recent Covid-19 infection and poor management of health care regulations in the country may have cost him some votes.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
