<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Forty</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Forty</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 20 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Covid 19 Mortality</title>
      <link>/projects/project2/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/project2/</guid>
      <description>Analysis of mortality rates based on several input variables On this page, we are going to look in more detail at the deadliness of Covid-19. We know that the virus has spread across the world over the last few months, sending terror into the minds of billions worldwide. However, is it as deadly as we think it is? Is there evidence to show that people must be extremely worried about this virus.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Does the Yield Curve Predict a Recession?</title>
      <link>/projects/project4/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/project4/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Every so often, we hear warnings from commentators on the “inverted yield curve” and its predictive power with respect to recessions. An explainer what a inverted yield curve is can be found here. If you’d rather listen to something, here is a great podcast from NPR on yield curve indicators.
In addition, many articles and commentators think that, e.g., Yield curve inversion is viewed as a harbinger of recession.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Donald Trump&#39;s Approval Rating</title>
      <link>/projects/project3/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/project3/</guid>
      <description>My forecast of what is coming! America is in a state of political, economic and social turmoil. And the election still hasn’t happened yet! This page looks at Donald Trump’s approval amongst his voters and how it has changed since Biden has become the confirmed Democratic candidate. Biden is ahead in the polls as of today so are we in for a new President? The race is on. Four years after Trump’s historic election victory, the time has come again this November - the 52 American states will elect a new president.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Session 2: Homework 1</title>
      <link>/projects/project6/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/project6/</guid>
      <description>On your own: IBM HR Analytics For this task, you will analyse a data set on Human Resoruce Analytics. The IBM HR Analytics Employee Attrition &amp;amp; Performance data set is a fictional data set created by IBM data scientists. Among other things, the data set includes employees’ income, their distance from work, their position in the company, their level of education, etc. A full description can be found on the website.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Session 6: Homework 3</title>
      <link>/projects/project5/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/project5/</guid>
      <description>IMDB ratings: Differences between directors We explore whether the mean IMDB rating for Steven Spielberg and Tim Burton are the same or not. The confidence intervals for the mean ratings of these two directors overlap.
First, we will reproduce the graph above.
In addition, we will run a hypothesis test, using use both the t.test command and the infer package to simulate from a null distribution, assuming zero difference between the two.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Aliquam</title>
      <link>/blogs/aliquam/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2017 22:42:51 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blogs/aliquam/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tempus</title>
      <link>/blogs/tempus/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2017 22:26:13 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blogs/tempus/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Magna</title>
      <link>/blogs/magna/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2017 22:26:09 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blogs/magna/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Curriculum Vitae</title>
      <link>/blogs/blog1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2017 21:28:43 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blogs/blog1/</guid>
      <description>Don&amp;rsquo;t miss out on an excellent hiring opportunity!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello R Markdown</title>
      <link>/post/2015-07-23-r-rmarkdown/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jul 2015 21:13:14 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2015-07-23-r-rmarkdown/</guid>
      <description>R Markdown This is an R Markdown document. Markdown is a simple formatting syntax for authoring HTML, PDF, and MS Word documents. For more details on using R Markdown see http://rmarkdown.rstudio.com.
You can embed an R code chunk like this:
summary(cars) ## speed dist ## Min. : 4.0 Min. : 2.00 ## 1st Qu.:12.0 1st Qu.: 26.00 ## Median :15.0 Median : 36.00 ## Mean :15.4 Mean : 42.98 ## 3rd Qu.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
